Hello, all my friends, and welcome to exercise number 73.
We are asked to write a function that finds the sum of nodes in a circle of link, at least.
So how to do that?
I want from you to post the video and start thinking about it and write this solution in the comments
below.
So how to find it a function to find some of the given circle and kid list we need to return.
Its returning type would be integer, and that's called some.
Find some.
In fact, there's no the.
We start from the have to start making this up.
So first of all, I will create A..
That it is them that we are going to traverse it because we need to make them equal to have and and
some equal to zero.
Then if had the does not equal to null, then we are going to make a do.
I loop that traverse throughout the elements and add them so damp.
The next we are going to move the cursor temp.
So our jumping this cursor, we are moving it to that next one and update the some by making at some,
the old sum is equal to then use some here, then use some is equal to the old sum plus that damp that
date.
OK.
And we specify while Tampa does not equal content and this is the stumbling, stumbling condition of
the circular link, at least that indicates that we have reached the end of their list.
OK, then return.
So let's run and see bioprinting here.
System that out, dot, print and just some of this off nodes would be.
We are calling find some.
Okay.
We specify the head as it's let's let's run at the sum of nodes is 17 to five, six, 12 and plus five.
It would be seven.
And there we go.
We have find it.
And since we are traversing through all the elements of this of this link, at least Circle Link Atlas,
so we need to find the out.
It's time complexity would be all off of all of what all of and because we are traversing through all
the news.
OK.
Its worst case scenario, its best case scenario is of one.
If we have only one note and the worst case scenario is oh fine, one million one thousand one hundred
or whatever notes.
And we are going to find this.
So in this way, we have to find some.
I need from you a favor to rate us five stars and use them to keep us making and uploading.